

Jr. Phillip von Leonard, San Borja, Lima - Corpac



Franshesca_94@hotmail.com

SUMMARY -

To start connecting with users like you, I decided to study on LABORATORIA with an agile learning workflow; i have experience on responsive web design, User Interface, mockups and research; Within this field I specialize on personal interviews and recollection of data for an excellent product. Highly empathize customer's needs to make a user-friendly yet appealing and simple solutions for company success and repeat bussiness

REDES SOCIALES —



franshescaqm

M Franshesca Quezada

FRANSHESCA QUEZADA MONZÓN

UX DESIGNER JR.

EXPERIENCE

BILINGUAL OPERATOR

PANASH S.A.C / MIRAFLORES, PERU/ FEB 2016 - SEP 2017

I worked as an Online Casino customer service agent and received various claims through live chat, phone and e-mail from USA, European and Peruvian customers; In order to process their claims, we had internal coordination by email with various areas. Main functions: Analize cases through customer´s personal profile, sending detailed case information to main areas, follow up on assigned Back-Office duties

OFFICE ASSISTANT

SUNAT/MIRAFLORES, PERU/OCT 2014 - SEP 2015

Worked on SUNAT on the Tax collections area. My main functions consisted organizing the resolution letters for national departure. Responsible of internal coordinations with the courier companies: SERPOST and PITS. As well as data and document filing. Preparing excel data for documentation already shipped and organizing company events.

SECURITY OPERATOR OF CONTROL CENTER

TELEFÓNICA DEL PERÚ S.A.A / SURQUILLO, PERU / SEP 2013 – JUL 2014

My first job consisted attending the internal security of one of the most important comunication Company in Peru. The functions that I executed were being in charge of the security agents, checking the security camera in case of incidents, support and coordination to the internal client in case of contingencies, activation and deactivation of personnel access cards for common and restricted areas through the BOSCH system, and alarm testing through the fire panel.

REFERENCES

Jessica Sarmiento Benavides Head of Information Security and Fraud Prevention

#944657509 – TIS (TELEFONICA INGENERIA DE SEGURIDAD) Lucy Kau Kau Administrative Management Supervisor

992925039 – COACTIVE COLLECTION MANAGEMENT (SUNAT)



SOFT SKILLS

- ✓ RESILENCE
- ✓ RESPONSABILITY
- ✓ PERSEVERANCE
- ✓ TEAMWORK
- ✓ HONESTY

HOBBIES -



I have a published poem released with the help of my school along with other interstate Young poets – USA, NJ 2007

REDES SOCIALES—

- in Franshesca Quezada
- franshescaqm
- M Franshesca Quezada

FRANSHESCA QUEZADA MONZÓN

UX DESIGNER JR.

EDUCATION

UX DESIGN

LABORATORIA / SEPT 2017 - MAR 2018

FIGMA

MARVEL

O CUANTITATIVE – CUALITATIVE RESEARCH

O HTML5 - CSS3

FRAMEWORK: BOOTSTRAP – MATERIALIZE

BASIC JQUERY AND JS

ENGLISH LANGUAGE

ICPNA / 2010 - 2011

O GRAMMAR

O SPEAKING

O WRITING

, vvi(iiiii)

HIGH SCHOOL EDUCATION PERU

JOHN NEPPER/CONCLUDED 2011

PRIMARY / MIDDLE SCHOOL EDUCATION USA,NJ

RED BANK PRIMARY SCHOOL - RED BANK CHARTE SCHOOL / 2002 - 2006